// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from ".";

export const sideProjects: Topic = {
  topic: "Side Projects",
  level: "Beginner",
  totalQuestions: 40,
  totalScore: 200,
  totalTime: 3600,
  questions: [
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the 2nd full-length album by The Prize Fighter Inferno?",
      choices: [
        "Half Measures",
        "The City Introvert",
        "My Brother's Blood Machine",
        "Before They Bury Me",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The City Introvert"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Fire Deuce is a side project of which member of Coheed and Cambria?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Travis Stever",
        "Josh Eppard",
        "Zach Cooper",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Travis Stever"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What was the original name of Davenport Cabinet?",
      choices: [
        "The Pink Panther",
        "The English Panther",
        "Deuce Cabinet",
        "Weerd Science",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The English Panther"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the rapper Weerd Science?",
      choices: ["Travis Stever", "Joey Eppard", "Zach Cooper", "Josh Eppard"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Josh Eppard"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the lead singer of L.S. Dunes?",
      choices: [
        "Anthony Green",
        "Zach Cooper",
        "Joey Eppard",
        "Claudio Sanchez",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Anthony Green"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the boxer who goes by the name The Prize Fighter Inferno?",
      choices: ["West Coast Devin", "Mike Tyson", "Jesse", "Claudio"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Jesse"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What other band is L.S. Dunes guitarist Frank Iero a member of?",
      choices: [
        "Circa Survive",
        "The Sound of Animals Fighting",
        "Thursday",
        "My Chemical Romance",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["My Chemical Romance"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of Davenport Cabinet's 2nd album?",
      choices: [
        "Nostalgia In Stereo",
        "Our Machine",
        "Damned Renegades",
        "Risks in Magic",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Nostalgia In Stereo"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "Whose side project is called The Prize Fighter Inferno?",
      choices: [
        "Travis Stever",
        "Zach Cooper",
        "Josh Eppard",
        "Claudio Sanchez",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Sanchez"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of a band Zach Cooper was in before Coheed and Cambria?",
      choices: ["Nirvana", "Afterman", "Inferno", "Life Before This"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Life Before This"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno is a solo project by which member of Coheed and Cambria?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Travis Stever",
        "Josh Eppard",
        "Zach Cooper",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Sanchez"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of The Prize Fighter Inferno's debut album, released in 2006?",
      choices: [
        "Half Measures",
        "My Brother's Blood Machine",
        "The Going Price for Home",
        "Gutter Phenomenon",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["My Brother's Blood Machine"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno's song 'Easter' is part of a concept album. What is the title of this concept album?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "The Afterman: Descension",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Afterman: Ascension"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In The Prize Fighter Inferno's song 'The Margretville Dance,' the protagonist travels to a fictional place. What is the name of this place?",
      choices: [
        "Margretville",
        "Hell's Kitchen",
        "The Dark Sentencer",
        "Wonderland",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Margretville"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno released a Christmas-themed EP in 2009. What is the title of this EP?",
      choices: [
        "Merry Christmas",
        "The Christmas Chronicles",
        "Deck the Halls",
        "Half Measures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Half Measures"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of The Prize Fighter Inferno's second full-length album, released in 2019?",
      choices: [
        "The Going Price for Home",
        "Thief",
        "In the Clear",
        "More Better",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Thief"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno's EP 'Gears' was released in 2005. What animated series inspired the song 'Gears'?",
      choices: ["Rick and Morty", "Adventure Time", "The Simpsons", "Futurama"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Simpsons"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In The Prize Fighter Inferno's song 'Pistol Pete Matty,' what instrument is prominently featured?",
      choices: ["Banjo", "Accordion", "Mandolin", "Trumpet"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Banjo"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno's EP 'Gears' includes a song with a cover of a classic track. Which song is covered on this EP?",
      choices: [
        "Bohemian Rhapsody by Queen",
        "Dream On by Aerosmith",
        "Wish You Were Here by Pink Floyd",
        "Rocket Man by Elton John",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Rocket Man by Elton John"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno's album 'Thief' features a song inspired by a popular video game. Which game is it?",
      choices: [
        "The Legend of Zelda",
        "Final Fantasy",
        "Super Mario Bros.",
        "World of Warcraft",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Legend of Zelda"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Davenport Cabinet is a side project led by which member of Coheed and Cambria?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Travis Stever",
        "Josh Eppard",
        "Zach Cooper",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Travis Stever"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Davenport Cabinet's debut album, released in 2007?",
      choices: [
        "Our Machine",
        "Nostalgia in Stereo",
        "Damned Renegades",
        "Risk and Reward",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Our Machine"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2013, Davenport Cabinet released an album featuring a song that serves as a sequel to a Coheed and Cambria track. What is the title of this song?",
      choices: [
        "The Margretville Dance",
        "Sons of Belial",
        "Here's Looking at You, Kid",
        "Expector",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Sons of Belial"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Davenport Cabinet's album 'Damned Renegades' includes a song that shares its title with a classic novel. Which novel is it?",
      choices: [
        "Moby-Dick",
        "The Great Gatsby",
        "To Kill a Mockingbird",
        "1984",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Moby-Dick"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of the EP released by Davenport Cabinet in 2018?",
      choices: [
        "Risks in Magic",
        "Murmuration",
        "Live at Dingbatz",
        "Carousel",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Risks in Magic"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Davenport Cabinet's song 'Simple Worlds' was featured in the soundtrack of which video game?",
      choices: [
        "Bioshock Infinite",
        "The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim",
        "Red Dead Redemption 2",
        "Fallout 4",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Fallout 4"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2010, Davenport Cabinet released a split EP with another band. Which band was it?",
      choices: [
        "Circa Survive",
        "Thank You Scientist",
        "RX Bandits",
        "The Dear Hunter",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["RX Bandits"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Davenport Cabinet's third full-length album, released in 2021?",
      choices: [
        "Our Machine II",
        "Blessed Shivs",
        "Curator",
        "Multitude of Stars",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Multitude of Stars"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Davenport Cabinet's song 'Sister Servant' is inspired by the works of which famous author?",
      choices: [
        "J.R.R. Tolkien",
        "H.P. Lovecraft",
        "Ray Bradbury",
        "Arthur C. Clarke",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["H.P. Lovecraft"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the significance of the title 'Davenport Cabinet' for the band?",
      choices: [
        "It's named after a street in Claudio Sanchez's hometown",
        "It's a tribute to a childhood friend",
        "It's a reference to a historical event",
        "It's a nod to a fictional character in 'The Amory Wars'",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: [
        "It's named after a street in Claudio Sanchez's hometown",
      ],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Weerd Science is a side project led by which member of Coheed and Cambria?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Travis Stever",
        "Josh Eppard",
        "Zach Cooper",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Josh Eppard"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Weerd Science's debut album, released in 2005?",
      choices: [
        "The Waterfront EP",
        "Friends and Nervous Breakdowns",
        "Red Light Juliet",
        "Sick Kids",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Friends and Nervous Breakdowns"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2013, Weerd Science released an EP containing a song featuring a guest appearance by a member of another band. Who was the guest musician?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Travis Stever",
        "Chino Moreno",
        "Maynard James Keenan",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Chino Moreno"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Weerd Science's song 'Conspiracy Theories Without Mel Gibson' is part of which EP?",
      choices: [
        "The Waterfront EP",
        "Sick Kids",
        "Red Light Juliet",
        "Friends and Nervous Breakdowns",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Waterfront EP"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Weerd Science's third full-length album, released in 2018?",
      choices: [
        "The Waterfront EP",
        "Red Light Juliet",
        "Ruin Your Life",
        "Red Light Juliet Part 2",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Red Light Juliet Part 2"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Weerd Science's song 'Kill It With Fire' is part of the soundtrack for which video game?",
      choices: [
        "Grand Theft Auto V",
        "Call of Duty: Modern Warfare",
        "Fallout 4",
        "The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Fallout 4"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2019, Weerd Science released a single with a cover of a classic song. Which song did they cover?",
      choices: [
        "Bohemian Rhapsody by Queen",
        "Billie Jean by Michael Jackson",
        "Dream On by Aerosmith",
        "The Sound of Silence by Simon & Garfunkel",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Billie Jean by Michael Jackson"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Weerd Science's EP 'Sick Kids' includes a collaboration with a member of another band. Who is the guest musician?",
      choices: [
        "Travis Stever",
        "Chino Moreno",
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Maynard James Keenan",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Travis Stever"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Weerd Science's second full-length album, released in 2011?",
      choices: [
        "Red Light Juliet",
        "Sick Kids",
        "The Waterfront EP",
        "Ruin Your Life",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Ruin Your Life"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Weerd Science's song 'Blueprints for Future Homes' is part of which EP?",
      choices: [
        "Friends and Nervous Breakdowns",
        "Sick Kids",
        "Red Light Juliet",
        "The Waterfront EP",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Friends and Nervous Breakdowns"],
      score: 5,
    },
  ],
};
